http://cubbyholetoys.com/privacy

Search for:
Search
Account Login |
New Wholesaler Registration
Home / Privacy Policy
We collect personal information primarily so that we may process your order, but also so that we may personalize your purchases and make your shopping experience as unique as possible. In addition to personal information collected for purposes of processing your order, we may ask for the following information:
BILLING AND SHIPPING INFORMATION
During the checkout process, we ask for certain personal information – name, address, e-mail, telephone number and credit card information – all of which are necessary for us to process your order and ship it to you. Basic personal information such as name, address and telephone number, but not credit card numbers, may be transmitted to contracted third parties ( Fed Ex, UPS, USPS, etc.) solely for the purpose of shipping your order.  As described , ordering with The Cubbyhole is safe and secure.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
In order to personalize your item, Cubbyhole requires that you submit certain private information to us on these items. This may consists of your child’s name(s) or age(s), birth date(s) etc. This information is used only to personalize your item, and is held strictly confidential.
EMAIL ADDRESSES
During the checkout process, we collect your e-mail address. Your e-mail address is used only so that you may receive offers and announcements via e-mail from The Cubbyhole and is not forwarded to any third parties.
Cubbyhole Toys
HomeAbout UsShopFAQReviewsContact Us
× Close Panel
This is a new web site so for security purposes you will need to reset your passwords.
As long as you use the same email and just reset password your account status will be the same.
Please contact me if you have any issues....thank you
Debi Dismiss
